itshot.com 2015-11-08

# ItsHot.com Privacy Policy

ItsHot is dedicated to provide their customers with exceptional customer service and outstanding value in fine jewelry. We are committed to maintain our customer's privacy to better serve you. We may collect and maintain certain information regarding, for example, your product and service preferences, dates of special occasions related to people you buy gifts for (e.g., birthdays), as  well as billing and shipping information. Nevertheless, under no circumstances do we sell or rent this information to other businesses. We strictly protect and enforce the confidentiality of this information. We do not participate in or contribute to cooperative or shared databases that give other companies access to information. In addition to the personal information that you may provide us with, this Site may use technology that lets us collect certain technical information such as, your Internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, your browser type, traffic patterns and the address of any referring Web Sites.

**Security**

ItsHot utilizes a number of security technologies and measures to assure the protection of your personal information when ordering over the net. All personal information will be kept confidential by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL encrypts your order information to prevent any improper use or inaccuracy of your personal information.

**Accuracy of collected data**

ItsHot will replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by ItsHot in connection with the operation of this Site, at your request. Cookies "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. ItsHot uses cookies on certain pages to determine the traffic on our site, measure promotional effectiveness, track visits from our affiliates and partners and allow the use of our shopping cart. We do not use cookies to save or gather any personal information.

**Minors**

No information may be submitted to the ItsHot.com by persons under the age of 18, nor may persons under the age of 18 make purchases or any other illegal acts on this Site without our consent.

**Refer a Friend**

Using ItsHot forms, you may refer a friend to our Web Site. You and your friend's names and e-mail addresses will be required so that your friend will be notified that you have asked that ItsHot send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will be used solely for this purpose unless consent is otherwise established.

**Changes**

We may change this Privacy Policy, modify or withdraw access to this Site or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice.

## Your Consent to our Privacy Policy

By using ItsHot.com, you agree to our privacy terms and conditions. We may occasionally update the current privacy policy, and therefore strongly encourage you to periodically review our policies to prevent any misinterpretations, as well as to stay informed about how we are protecting your information.

This site uses data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics.

The Google Analytics features this site's implemented based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en-GB&sig=ACi0TCg56kW4pF3t60Ll-wJMxUIj-WjTCW_UHtqb9kUH49UY-ig5Tt3BarVsiqRVidxxA7oP-AKDet4y753jZuKxtnO7bhfTKjolyQLYZ6NZv64hNBAl0EqcIl4Px_fAQwWdx-67DOv6C27fIZCL-IH0P0u82_L9wvyH5YKpng6M7BIN7W2SS2l59cABrHL--Rx2wkcRMEl6DyBH9BFxOZjDeNHTjfKH0jW66w-NVIRuXc3A5ctz6I1rmws5u6GrVitGReLLh12E), you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.
